To report a problem with a product detail page, open the Seller Central Main menu, hover over Performance,
click "Account Health".
Then, in the top left-hand corner of the Account Health page, select "Report Abuse of Amazon Policies".
You'll see a series of reporting options in a menu on the left, including multiple options related
to product detail pages.
Click "Product Detail Page" violates Amazon's policies or is misleading customers.
Then, select the option that most closely aligns with the issue you encountered.
You'll need to provide the ASIN attached to the product or products and a description of the problem.
Then, click "Submit".
We will review your submission and update you when a course of action has been determined.